Will subscribers to the store be re-rendered if you compose the worst the other?
Yeah, I'm thinking it was a miracle. They asked it so most of them during the
Yeah, okay, so I'll answer that because I think that's an interesting question
It itself and then if they clarify otherwise
So this is one thing I do think view does really well because of the way the reactivity see reactivity system is written with proxies
view
very rarely like so like to be honest. I know like reactives with this a lot which is like you have some state derived from this other state
And because this state updates it triggers the re-render on this other state and so it's like reforming thing that they frequently have to deal with
But put me on and people for those of us that use view that's actually very
I don't see I don't know everything. It's an issue just because again
Because view understands that like yes, you're composing your source together
They're responded they're dependent on each other
But if it's not an a context where rendering is necessary it shouldn't like unless you're triggering an update that goes up that way like intentionally
You're really just calling a value to be there to derive another value
And so they're usually very good about
And so that's one of the things that if you haven't heard about view vapor
This is a big thing that's coming
to like
Basically they are we're gonna be able to render your project without the virtual dome and the performance boosts on this are supposed to be quite promising benchmark wise
And so
Because the whole idea is that you're supposed to be able to differentiate when a
Value actually is gonna touch a template like the tree versus us a value that's
You know in some sort of dependency tree and so the I know Evan and the team have done a lot of
granular work to figure out ways to really make sure that you don't get random
triggering every rendering and that kind of thing
So again if there's if you're all are for those if you want to be you know very
Forward facing and keep up to date with the lazy greatest definitely follow view vapor to find out what everyone's doing. It's pretty cool
Is that what the
On the femur was asking about that's exactly what they were asking
They said they face this a lot in react
Yeah, it's
It's unfortunate
Yeah, one of the things that we see a lot of frameworks doing these days is honestly if you've looked at angular solids felt like it does seem like a lot of the modern
Framework's are trying to converge in terms of the ideas and they seem to agree
In terms of reactivity principles like I think
I mean angular jump them more with this too, so of angular solid view things fells on here too
I think all four are on board with signals
So that's basically an agreed reactivity approach and then there is there is this general sense that like computed
Which is a derived part of state that has built in memoization and then optimizations in it is a key part because as developers
That's what we're doing half the time we have single source of truth. We derive stuff. We derive stuff. We derive stuff
We don't really want to have to deal with the memoization and the caching that deals in that like we have other things to worry about and so I think if you're looking at the proposals on the like
Web or TC they're nine and stuff
There's a native signals proposal, but then within the individual frameworks like I think angular right now is calling it link signals
I think solid did too, but they're all it's it's really cool to see a lot of these frameworks starting to centralize
And kind of agree on what what what is the best practice for the web, so that is super exciting